allfinancialforms.com 2010-11-22

# Our Privacy policy – All Financial Forms « All Financial Forms

Our Privacy Policy:

Who we are: AllFinancialForms.com provides financial forms that are available in the market. It’s a collection and transfer of consumer information. We have kept all the sections open so that people can add any new. Necessary password will have to be collected for edition; people can ask for this to the webmaster concerned.

Information we collect: The forms available in allfinancialforms.com are collected from different sources (govt. and other authorized agencies) and are placed for the visitors convenience.

How our privacy policy is monitored: For giving access to edit pages we require your personal information and we guarantee that the information will not be neither used for any other purposes nor given to anybody else. We may attempt to contact you in case of any misuse happens on handling allfinancialforms.com pages. In such cases we may also block your password for editing / using our pages.

Changes to this Policy or additional information: If you have any questions or concerns on our privacy policy, please contact at webmaster(at)allfinancialforms.com We will update the new policies with the date of effect if management finds it useful.

Important Points: The forms are provided for your convenience and are not the substitute for the advice of an attorney. Please use these forms at your own risk. No representation or warranty as to legality, correctness or acceptance or accuracy of these forms by any State or jurisdiction is indicated. Please check with your local court house or consult an attorney to ensure accuracy before using these forms. Legal Advice should always be sought from legal counsel in the relevant jurisdiction
